Something interesting happened to me
with this show, which was, I
had a kind of quite comfortable way of
doing this show that I put together,
which
involved showing a whole bunch of
different books and
talking about each book, which it was
kind of devolving into a PowerPoint
presentation.
And I did some kind of early versions
of the show in
London at a kind of a fringe theatre,
and I held all the books in a
suitcase. And I left them somewhere on
the London.
The London Underground features quite
heavily in this.
And the London Underground, the
subconscious, I probably quite closely
related
anyway. But anyway, some part of me
decided that that wasn't the way
to do this show and left those books
on the Victoria line, I think.
So kind of like, were they destroyed
in the controlled explosion?
I don't know.